<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>游뛌 Walking Routes on Seattle Routes</title>
    <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 游뛌 Walking Routes on Seattle Routes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:10:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Center 游대 Olympic Sculpture Park 游대 Pike Place Market 游대 The Spheres Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/seattlecenter-olympicsculpturepark-pikeplace-spheres-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:10:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/seattlecenter-olympicsculpturepark-pikeplace-spheres-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Begin your scenic walking adventure at the iconic Seattle Center, home to the famous Space Needle and vibrant Chihuly Garden and Glass. From here, head west towards the waterfront, making your way to the Olympic Sculpture Park. This expansive, open-air museum offers a delightful blend of contemporary art and natural beauty, with breathtaking views of Puget Sound and the Olympic Mountains.&#xA;Continue south along the waterfront, soaking in the sights and sounds of the bustling Elliott Bay Trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Union Loop (Lake Union Park 游대 Gas Works Park 游대 UW)</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/lake-union-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:24:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/lake-union-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at the Museum of History &amp;amp; Industry (MOHAI) in South Lake Union, this scenic loop around Lake Union offers a variety of activities and sights. Begin your journey with a visit to MOHAI, where you can explore exhibits on Seattle&amp;rsquo;s rich history and innovation.&#xA;From MOHAI, walk along the lake&amp;rsquo;s edge heading northwest towards Gas Works Park. As you make your way, enjoy the bustling atmosphere of South Lake Union Park, where you can rent a kayak or paddleboard to experience the lake up close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Volunteer Park 游대 Washington Park Arboretum Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:02:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting from South Lake Union (SLU), this scenic loop takes you through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most beautiful green spaces and vibrant neighborhoods. Begin your journey in SLU, where you can enjoy the lively atmosphere of the waterfront area. Consider grabbing a coffee or a quick bite at one of the many cafes and restaurants in the neighborhood before you set off.&#xA;Head east from SLU towards Volunteer Park. As you make your way through the city streets, you&amp;rsquo;ll pass through the bustling Capitol Hill neighborhood, known for its eclectic mix of shops, cafes, and cultural spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Spheres 游대 MOHAI 游대 Space Needle Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/spheres-mohai-spaceneedle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 19:22:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/spheres-mohai-spaceneedle/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at The Spheres, this walking loop provides a unique tour through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most iconic landmarks. Begin your journey with a visit to The Spheres, where you can explore the lush, indoor gardens filled with exotic plants and enjoy a tranquil oasis in the heart of the city.&#xA;From The Spheres, head towards the Museum of History &amp;amp; Industry (MOHAI) in South Lake Union. The walk takes you through vibrant city streets and along the waterfront, offering beautiful views of Lake Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Lumen Field Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-lumen-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 22:44:17 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-lumen-field/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at South Lake Union, this walking loop offers a comprehensive tour of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s iconic landmarks and vibrant neighborhoods. Begin your journey in SLU, where you can enjoy the lakeside parks and bustling waterfront. Consider grabbing a coffee at one of the many cafes in the area before setting off.&#xA;Head south towards Pike Place Market, one of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most famous attractions. As you make your way, enjoy the lively streets filled with shops and eateries.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
