<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Seattle Routes</title>
    <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Seattle Routes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 08:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://seattleroutes.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Center 游대 Olympic Sculpture Park 游대 Pike Place Market 游대 The Spheres Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/seattlecenter-olympicsculpturepark-pikeplace-spheres-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:10:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/seattlecenter-olympicsculpturepark-pikeplace-spheres-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Begin your scenic walking adventure at the iconic Seattle Center, home to the famous Space Needle and vibrant Chihuly Garden and Glass. From here, head west towards the waterfront, making your way to the Olympic Sculpture Park. This expansive, open-air museum offers a delightful blend of contemporary art and natural beauty, with breathtaking views of Puget Sound and the Olympic Mountains.&#xA;Continue south along the waterfront, soaking in the sights and sounds of the bustling Elliott Bay Trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Log Boom Park Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-logboom-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 15:19:16 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-logboom-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description The SLU 游대 Log Boom Park Loop begins in the vibrant neighborhood of South Lake Union (SLU), known for its modern vibe and stunning views of Lake Union. From SLU, you head north along the edge of Lake Union, enjoying the scenic waterfront, and make your way to the iconic Gas Works Park. Here, you can take in the unique industrial structures and panoramic views of the Seattle skyline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Volunteer Park 游대 Washington Park Arboretum Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:32:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting from South Lake Union (SLU), this scenic loop takes you through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most beautiful green spaces and vibrant neighborhoods. Begin your journey in SLU, where you can enjoy the lively atmosphere of the waterfront area. Consider grabbing a coffee or a quick bite at one of the many cafes and restaurants in the neighborhood before you set off.&#xA;Head east from SLU towards Volunteer Park. As you make your way through the city streets, you&amp;rsquo;ll pass through the bustling Capitol Hill neighborhood, known for its eclectic mix of shops, cafes, and cultural spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Union Loop (Lake Union Park 游대 Gas Works Park 游대 UW)</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/lake-union-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/lake-union-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at the Museum of History &amp;amp; Industry (MOHAI) in South Lake Union, this scenic loop around Lake Union offers a variety of activities and sights. Begin your journey with a visit to MOHAI, where you can explore exhibits on Seattle&amp;rsquo;s rich history and innovation.&#xA;From MOHAI, walk along the lake&amp;rsquo;s edge heading northwest towards Gas Works Park. As you make your way, enjoy the bustling atmosphere of South Lake Union Park, where you can rent a kayak or paddleboard to experience the lake up close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Union Loop (Lake Union Park 游대 Gas Works Park 游대 UW)</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/lake-union-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:24:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/lake-union-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at the Museum of History &amp;amp; Industry (MOHAI) in South Lake Union, this scenic loop around Lake Union offers a variety of activities and sights. Begin your journey with a visit to MOHAI, where you can explore exhibits on Seattle&amp;rsquo;s rich history and innovation.&#xA;From MOHAI, walk along the lake&amp;rsquo;s edge heading northwest towards Gas Works Park. As you make your way, enjoy the bustling atmosphere of South Lake Union Park, where you can rent a kayak or paddleboard to experience the lake up close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Volunteer Park 游대 Washington Park Arboretum Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:02:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting from South Lake Union (SLU), this scenic loop takes you through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most beautiful green spaces and vibrant neighborhoods. Begin your journey in SLU, where you can enjoy the lively atmosphere of the waterfront area. Consider grabbing a coffee or a quick bite at one of the many cafes and restaurants in the neighborhood before you set off.&#xA;Head east from SLU towards Volunteer Park. As you make your way through the city streets, you&amp;rsquo;ll pass through the bustling Capitol Hill neighborhood, known for its eclectic mix of shops, cafes, and cultural spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Spheres 游대 MOHAI 游대 Space Needle Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/spheres-mohai-spaceneedle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 19:22:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/spheres-mohai-spaceneedle/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at The Spheres, this walking loop provides a unique tour through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most iconic landmarks. Begin your journey with a visit to The Spheres, where you can explore the lush, indoor gardens filled with exotic plants and enjoy a tranquil oasis in the heart of the city.&#xA;From The Spheres, head towards the Museum of History &amp;amp; Industry (MOHAI) in South Lake Union. The walk takes you through vibrant city streets and along the waterfront, offering beautiful views of Lake Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Woodinville Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-woodinville/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 11:53:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-woodinville/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting from South Lake Union, this 43.7-mile biking route takes you through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most scenic and bike-friendly paths. Begin your journey by heading northeast via the Burke-Gilman Trail. This well-maintained trail offers beautiful views of Lake Union and Lake Washington, making it a popular choice for cyclists.&#xA;As you follow the trail, you&amp;rsquo;ll pass through the University of Washington campus. Consider taking a short detour to explore the beautiful grounds, including Drumheller Fountain and the Burke Museum of Natural History and Culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Lumen Field Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-lumen-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 22:44:17 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/walking/slu-lumen-field/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at South Lake Union, this walking loop offers a comprehensive tour of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s iconic landmarks and vibrant neighborhoods. Begin your journey in SLU, where you can enjoy the lakeside parks and bustling waterfront. Consider grabbing a coffee at one of the many cafes in the area before setting off.&#xA;Head south towards Pike Place Market, one of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most famous attractions. As you make your way, enjoy the lively streets filled with shops and eateries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&#xA;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 1</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.&#xA;Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
