<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>游뛊 Biking Routes on Seattle Routes</title>
    <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 游뛊 Biking Routes on Seattle Routes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:32:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Volunteer Park 游대 Washington Park Arboretum Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:32:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-volunteer-park-washington-park-arboretum-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting from South Lake Union (SLU), this scenic loop takes you through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most beautiful green spaces and vibrant neighborhoods. Begin your journey in SLU, where you can enjoy the lively atmosphere of the waterfront area. Consider grabbing a coffee or a quick bite at one of the many cafes and restaurants in the neighborhood before you set off.&#xA;Head east from SLU towards Volunteer Park. As you make your way through the city streets, you&amp;rsquo;ll pass through the bustling Capitol Hill neighborhood, known for its eclectic mix of shops, cafes, and cultural spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Union Loop (Lake Union Park 游대 Gas Works Park 游대 UW)</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/lake-union-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/lake-union-loop/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting at the Museum of History &amp;amp; Industry (MOHAI) in South Lake Union, this scenic loop around Lake Union offers a variety of activities and sights. Begin your journey with a visit to MOHAI, where you can explore exhibits on Seattle&amp;rsquo;s rich history and innovation.&#xA;From MOHAI, walk along the lake&amp;rsquo;s edge heading northwest towards Gas Works Park. As you make your way, enjoy the bustling atmosphere of South Lake Union Park, where you can rent a kayak or paddleboard to experience the lake up close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLU 游대 Woodinville Loop</title>
      <link>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-woodinville/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 11:53:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seattleroutes.github.io/biking/slu-woodinville/</guid>
      <description>Route Description Starting from South Lake Union, this 43.7-mile biking route takes you through some of Seattle&amp;rsquo;s most scenic and bike-friendly paths. Begin your journey by heading northeast via the Burke-Gilman Trail. This well-maintained trail offers beautiful views of Lake Union and Lake Washington, making it a popular choice for cyclists.&#xA;As you follow the trail, you&amp;rsquo;ll pass through the University of Washington campus. Consider taking a short detour to explore the beautiful grounds, including Drumheller Fountain and the Burke Museum of Natural History and Culture.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
